<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.WP>WP</LegacyFairy.UI.WP>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.disabled_LowWP>Low WP</LegacyFairy.UI.disabled_LowWP>
  <LegacyFairy.UI.disabled_Down>Dont move</LegacyFairy.UI.disabled_Down>
  <LegacyFairy.UI.disabled_Cooldown>Cooldown</LegacyFairy.UI.disabled_Cooldown>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.label_BrillianceCharge>Brilliance Charge</LegacyFairy.UI.label_BrillianceCharge>
  <LegacyFairy.UI.desc_BrillianceCharge>It uses the power of brilliance to greatly reduce the time it takes to fire a shot.\n\n1WP is consumed per second.</LegacyFairy.UI.desc_BrillianceCharge>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.label_PrayertoDestiny>Prayer to Destiny</LegacyFairy.UI.label_PrayertoDestiny>
  <LegacyFairy.UI.desc_PrayertoDestiny>Drop any item or creature (except for some) in a drop pot near the colony.\nThen, you spend WP according to the silver value of the dropped item.\n\nThe creature does not belong to anywhere and falls in a state of anesthesia.\n\nWhen an item is selected, it will try to summon up to the stack limit if it has extra WP.\n\nCoolDown:10Day</LegacyFairy.UI.desc_PrayertoDestiny>

  <LegacyFairy.Item.LetsWish>Prayer to Destiny!</LegacyFairy.Item.LetsWish>
  <LegacyFairy.Item.Summon>Summon</LegacyFairy.Item.Summon>
  <LegacyFairy.Item.DontWish>Prayers cannot be struck empty.</LegacyFairy.Item.DontWish>
  <LegacyFairy.Item.SoldOut>Oh, that's out of stock.</LegacyFairy.Item.SoldOut>
  <LegacyFairy.Item.WishEnd>A {0} has fallen on your colony.</LegacyFairy.Item.WishEnd>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.WPBad>Residual WP</LegacyFairy.UI.WPBad>
  <LegacyFairy.UI.WPBadDesc>When you use WP facilities, WP with negative effects will be accumulated in the surrounding area for a while. Consuming a lot of WP in a short period of time will attract bad events.</LegacyFairy.UI.WPBadDesc>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.CantCast>You must have at least a total of {0} silver in order to perform the conversion.</LegacyFairy.UI.CantCast>

  <LegacyFairy.UI.Wish>What do you want?</LegacyFairy.UI.Wish>
  
  <LegacyFairy.TOW.MeteorCharge>"Start chanting to summon the meteorite."</LegacyFairy.TOW.MeteorCharge>
  <LegacyFairy.TOW.MeteorChargeWarn>"Meteorite summoner chanting, 10 seconds left..."</LegacyFairy.TOW.MeteorChargeWarn>
  <LegacyFairy.TOW.MeteorCancel>"If unexpected damage is detected, the chanting is interrupted and the scale is reduced..."</LegacyFairy.TOW.MeteorCancel>

  <LgcF_TOW.BossDesc>-This boss is very defensive and all attacks do only 1 damage except before the charge of the big move.\n\n-When attacked, the boss will perform a timed explosion attack on enemies in sight. Always keep track of who is targeted.\n\n-Massive shooting turrets will fire explosive rounds that will reduce the maximum HP of the target area, so it is recommended to keep them out of range.\n\n-When the meteors signal is given, they will stop moving, so concentrate your attacks on them. If you fail to damage the boss a certain number of times within a certain period of time, the boss will deal a huge amount of damage to the entire area.</LgcF_TOW.BossDesc>

</LanguageData>